Guide to the Elayne Zalis video studies archive, [circa 1979-1997].
Zalis, Elayne video studies archive
- Series III. Alphabetic Subject Files
  - SIGGRAPH (Special Interest Group on Computer Graphics) (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - “The Pioneers Return to Dallas: SIGGRAPH 1990” advance program for the 17th International Conference on Computer Graphics and Interactive Techniques. 1990
  - Society for Cinema Studies (SCS) (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - “Society for Cinema Studies Annual Conference—1989” Conference program with E. Zalis’ notes.
    - 1989Conference schedules with E. Zalis’ notes (10pp, double-spaced)
    - Attendee information packet for 1989 SCS conference, including schedules, dining guides, member directory, maps, and participant survey.
  - Society of American Archivists (Chicago) (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - SAA member information and staff guide, 1990
    - SAA book catalog and member application form, Fall 1989
  - Southwest Alternative Media Project Houston, TX (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - “Southwest Alternative Media Project Media Bulletin” newsletter, Fall 1990
    - “Southwest Alternative Media Project Media Bulletin” newsletter, Summer 1990
    - “Southwest Alternative Media Project Media Bulletin” newsletter, Winter 1989
    - “Southwest Alternative Media Project Media Bulletin” newsletter, Spring 1990
    - “Southwest Alternative Media Project Media Bulletin” newsletter, Summer 1989
    - “Southwest Alternative Media Project Media Bulletin” newsletter, Fall 1989
    - “Independent Image III: A Conference Promoting the Art and Business of Feature Filmmaking in the Southwest and Mid-American Region,” conference information and registration brochure, 1989
  - Syracuse LAMP (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - “Lamp ’86,” Light Audio Media Programs, journal, 1986
    - Packet of bibliographies with notes video screenings and publications, sent to Zalis by John Orentlicher
  - Rea Tajiri (videomaker and curator) (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Letter to Zalis from Tej Hazarika, Asian Cinevision, May 31, 1990
    - Program for the Seventh Annual Asian American International Video Festival, 1989
    - Program for the Eighth Annual Asian American International Video Festival, 1990
  - Tanam Press (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Book catalog
  - Leslie Thornton, videomaker, filmmaker, instructor, distributor (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Essay by Thornton on video artwork “Peggy and Fred in Hell,” 8 pp “New Distributor Embraces the Avant-Garde,” brief article in The Independent, April 1990, photocopy.
  - Truck, Fred (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - empty folder
  - Twin Peaks (TV) (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - TV listing showing channels and episode description for Twin Peaks
  - UCLA Film and Television Archive (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - “Archive,” newsletter and calendar of the UCLA film and television archive. November / December 1990
    - Promotional flyer for premiere screening of restored version of Fritz Lang’s "Metropolis."
    - UCLA Film and Television Archive Calendar, September-November, 1990
  - University of Iowa Library (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Letter to Zalis from Cathy Larsen regarding video artworks available in the University of Iowa library system. Includes a list of titles and handwritten note from the librarian.
  - USA Film Festival, Dallas (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Participant information folder, including two festival programs, list of winners, schedule, and program for KidFilm festival. 1989
  - Verbun (Magazine – Computer graphics) (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Verbun 4.1 (Winter/Spring 1990). Computer art magazine. Promotional copy. Includes promotional letter from publisher.
  - Video and the Arts, S.F. (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Video and the Arts no. 11, Winter 1986
  - Video Data Bank, Chicago (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - “Video Drive-In Press Package,” including summer program guides, 1990
    - “Video Data Bank Listings Supplement,” 1988/1989Includes Zalis' notes.
    - “Video Data Bank Listings Supplement,” 1988Includes Zalis' notes.
    - “What Does She Want,” guide to programmed series of video artworks about gender
    - Information and correspondence with the Video Data Bank, including letter to Zalis from Maria Benfield.
  - Video Free America (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - “Video Free America Retrospective,” essay by Christine Tamblyn Packet of photocopied articles and readings on video art
  - Vintage TV (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Information about available series, 2 pages double-sided
    - Catalog of available series
    - “The TV Collector,” vol. 2 no. 41 (March/April 1989) Newsletter/zine
    - “Big Reel” No. 178, March 15, 1989, tabloid newsletter. Includes original mailing envelope.
    - “Video Yesteryear,” Supplement no. 42R. Includes mailing envelope and postcard from Zalis. 1989
  - Walker Art Center, Minneapolis (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - “Viewpoints,” guide to exhibit by Mary Lucier and Paul Kos, 1987. Includes general visitors guide to the center and catalog of available postcards, notecards, prints
  - Washington Project for the Arts (WPA) (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Informational and promotional pamphlets, including information about specific exhibitions and general information about the program
    - “The Tell-Tale Heart,” catalog for exhibit of artists Ken Little, James Luna, Judy Southerland, Pat Ward Williams, curated by Mel Watkin. 1990
    - “War and Memory in the Aftermath of Vietnam,” catalog for multidisciplinary exhibit, 1987
  - WGBH New Television Workshop Boston (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Informational packet outlining history of organization. Includes Zalis’ notes.
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, NY (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - “American Federation of Arts” film program, 1981
    - List of available publications and table of mail order charges, 1989 (2 pp, includes original mailing envelope)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Scholars-in-Residence Program Information packet and application forms, 1988
  - Wisconsin Center for Film and Theater Research (U. Wisc., Madison) (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Informational brochure and list of available feature films
  - Women Make Movies, NY (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - “News from Women Make Movies,” newsletter, 1990
    - Letter to Zalis from Robin Vachal, distribution assistant, regarding research materials, December 20, 1989
    - Letter to Zalis from Shawn Atkins, Intern, regarding loan of videotapes, 28 September, 1990
  - Woman’s Building L.A. (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Calendar and course catalog
    - Basic information about the Women’s Building and call for video programming
  - Zone Books (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Zone Books publisher catalog, Fall 1988
  - Women in the Director’s Chair, Chicago (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - “Lasting Evidence,” program for Women in the Director’s Chair 7th Annual Women’s Film and Video Conference, 1988
    - “Lasting Evidence,” calendar and program for Women in the Director’s Chair 7th Annual Women’s Film and Video Festival, 1988
    - “Risk,” program for Women in the Director’s Chair 8th Annual Women’s Film and Video Conference, 1989
    - “Risk,” calendar and program for Women in the Director’s Chair 8th Annual Women’s Film and Video Festival, 1989
    - 10th Annual Women’s Film and Video Festival call for entries, 1990
    - Information packet for Women in the Director’s Chair, including membership information and application forms, international video conversion standards chart, programs for “Risk” (1989) and “All the Angles” (1990), Women’s International Film and Video Festivals, and note to Zalis dated 5/21/1990. Includes original mailing envelope.
    - Note from Inez Wehrli, director, the International Television Association, with Zalis’ notes on reverse side
    - Note to Zalis from Gretchen Elsner Sommer regarding research information, dated March 31, 1989
  - Video Theory (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Packet of articles and readings assembled by Zalis. Includes Afterimage, December 1991, multiple photocopies of articles on video and television theory, bibliographical notes from Robert H, Demig “Kate and Allie”
- Series IV. Videos
  - Rape Stories Strosser, Margie, 1988; V-6163; Length: 00:25:00 (Box 7)
  - Flag Gibson, Linda, 1989; V-6163; Length: 00:24:00 (Box 7)
  - Joy Ride Oursler, Tony and Constance Dejong, 1988; V-6164; Length: 00:14:00 (Box 7)
  - Home of the Brave Anderson, Laurie, 1992; V-6165; Length: 00:90:00 (Box 7)
  - Brainwave Drawings Sobell, Nina, 1973-1983; V-6166 (Box 7)
    3 copies; see also V-6188
  - Some L.A. Video Pieces Sobell, Nina, 1972-1984; V-6166; Length: 00:50:00 (Box 7)
  - Skin Matrix Emshwiller, Ed, 1984; V-6167; Length: 00:15:00 (Box 7)
  - Art of Memory Vasulka, Woody, 1987; V-6167; Length: 00:35:00 (Box 7)
  - Artists’ Music Television:(multiple titles), V-6167; Length: 00:30:00 (Box 7)
  - Dances in Exile Shang, Ruby, V-6168 (Box 7)
    A Collaboration with filmmaker Howard Silver. Narrated by B.D. Wong.
  - La Femme à la Cafetière Wilson, Robert, V-6168 (Box 7)
    co-produced by Musèe d’Orsay.
  - Vacation II Connors, Betsy, V-6168 (Box 7)
  - Loose the Thread Way, Brenda, V-6168 (Box 7)
    choreographed for San Francisco dance company ODC
  - The Big Inning Darmek, Dennis, V-6168 (Box 7)
  - Buddha's Door Luby, Abby, V-6168 (Box 7)
  - Between the Lines Muntadas, 1979; V-6169; Length: 00:23:27 (Box 7)
  - Exile Cha, Teresa Hak Kyung, 1980; V-6170; Length: 00:50:00 (Box 7)
  - The Book of Days (featured on "Alive From Off Center") Monk, Meredith, 1988; V-6171; Length: 00:60:00 (Box 7)
  - Dance video Chase, Doris, V-6172 (Box 7)
  - Dance video Greenfield, Amy, V-6172 (Box 7)
  - interview Sherman, Cindy, V-6172 (Box 7)
  - Political Advertisements III, 1956–1992 Muntadas and Marshall Reese, V-6173; Length: 00:54:00 (Box 7)
  - Alive from Off Center; Alter Image; Dancing Hands, incl. Hip Hop Hands Prevailing Condition; Handshake seq. Ellen Fisher, 1988; V-6174 (Box 7)
  - Absolute Commitment: Two Portraits (P.I.) Alien Nation 9/18/86, 1986; V-6175 (Box 7)
  - Alive TV M. Riggs, V-6176 (Box 7)
  - Compilation, 1989–90 Sparling, Bonnie, 1990; V-6177; Length: 00:25:00 (Box 7)
  - Alive From Off Center: several shows, circa 1991, 1991; V-6178 (Box 7)
  - Theory of Achievement Hartley, Hal, V-6178 (Box 7)
  - Sun, Moon and Feather Zipp, Jane and Bob Rosen, V-6178 (Box 7)
  - Dinizulu and His African Dancers, V-6178 (Box 7)
  - Hart Island Chronology Minahan, Daniel, V-6178 (Box 7)
  - Sabda Reeves, Daniel, V-6178 (Box 7)
  - Alive From Off Center: several shows, circa 1991, V-6179 (Box 7)
  - V-6179 (Box 7)
  - The Shaman’s Journey Trujillo, Raoul, V-6179 (Box 7)
  - Dancebrazil Viera, Jelon, V-6179 (Box 7)
  - Undertow Eiko and Koma, V-6179 (Box 7)
  - Shorebirds Atlantic Eckert and Jenkins, V-6179 (Box 7)
  - The Black Dress Bromburg, Ellen, V-6179 (Box 7)
  - 29 Effeminate Gestures Goode, Joe, V-6179 (Box 7)
  - Steps Rybczynski, Zbigniew, V-6179 (Box 7)
  - The Street of Crocodiles: Intro by Laurie Anderson Brothers Quay, The, V-6179 (Box 7)
  - Rap City Rhapsody PBS- Produced and directed by Akili Buchanon, 1990; V-6180 (Box 7)
  - Alive from Off Center: Roseland works by: Wim Vandekeybus; Octavio Iturbe; Walter Verdin, 1990; V-6180 (Box 7)
  - Fade to Black Cokes, Tony, 1990; V-6181; Length: 00:33:00 (Box 7)
  - The Eternal Frame Ant Farm, 1975; V-6182; Length: 00:23:50 (Box 7)
  - Man With A Video Camera and Free Society Garrin, Paul, 1988; V-6183; Length: 00:10:00 (Box 7)
  - I Need Your Full Cooperation High, Kathy, 1989; V-6183; Length: 00:30:00 (Box 7)
  - Consider Anything, Only Don’t Cry De Michiel, Helen, 1987; V-6184; Length: 00:22:00 (Box 7)
  - Secret Horror Smith, Michael, 1980; V-6185; Length: 00:14:00 (Box 7)
  - Rec Room Smith, Michael, 1981; V-6185; Length: 00:14:00 (Box 7)
  - Born to be Sold: The Case of Baby M Rosler, Martha, 1988; V-6186; Length: 00:35:00 (Box 7)
  - New Year Soe, Valerie, 1987; V-6187; Length: 00:20:00 (Box 7)
  - Trick or Drink Green, Vanalyne, 1985; V-6187; Length: 00:20:00 (Box 7)
  - Brainwave Drawings: 1973–1983 Sobell, Nina, V-6188; 3 copies (Box 7)
  - Some L.A. Video Pieces: 1972–1984 Sobell, Nina, V-6189; 00:50:00 (3 copies) (Box 7)
  - Sphinxes Without Secrets Beatty, Maria, 1991; V-6191; Length: 00:58:00 (Box 7)
  - One Banana, Two Bananas Sternberg, Natalie, 1992; V-6192; Length: 00:32:00 (Box 7)
  - Family Album Berliner, Alan, 1986; V-6193; Length: 00:55:00 (Box 7)
  - The Dormitory (Le Dortoir) Girard, François, 1991; V-6193; Length: 00:53:00 (Box 7)
  - Double Take Hershman, Lynn, 1989; V-6193 (Box 7)
  - Split Lister, Ardelle, 1981; V-6194; Length: 00:22:00 (Box 7)
  - That’s It, Forget It Miller, Branda, 1985; V-6194; Length: 00:05:00 (Box 7)
  - In the Garden of Memory Anders, R., 1988; V-6194; Length: 00:20:00 (Box 7)
  - The Science of Empty Signs Anders, R., V-6194; Length: 00:06:00 (Box 7)
  - Change of Address De Michiel, Helen, 1986; V-6194; Length: 00:27:00 (Box 7)
  - Surburban Queen Faber, Mindy, 1985; V-6194; Length: 00:07:00 (Box 7)
  - alienNation Rankus, Edward, et al., 1979; V-6195; Length: 00:29:00 (Box 7)
  - Work of Art in the Age of Electronic Reproduction Buchanan, Nancy, V-6195; Length: 00:08:00 (Box 7)
  - How to Make Love to Your Television Set (live show) Davis, Douglas, V-6196 (Box 7)
  - Wonder Woman(12/78 first rough cut) Birnbaum, Dara, 1978; V-6197 (Box 7)
  - Kiss the Girls: Make Them Cry(12/78 first rough cut) Birnbaum, Dara, 1979; V-6197 (Box 7)
  - Leaving the 20th Century Almy, Max, 1982; V-6197; Length: 00:11:00 (Box 7)
  - Modern Love Almy, Max, 1982; V-6197 (Box 7)
  - Modern Marriage Almy, Max, 1980; V-6197; Length: 00:03:00 (Box 7)
  - Perfect Leader Almy, Max, 1983; V-6197; Length: 00:04:15 (Box 7)
  - Joan Does Dynasty Braverman, Joan, 1986; V-6198; Length: 00:31:00 (Box 7)
  - Vertical Roll Jonas, Joan, 1972; V-6198; Length: 00:20:00 (Box 7)
  - Selected Works: 1970–78 Wegman, William, 1981; V-6198; Length: 00:19:00 (Box 7)
  - Turn Here Sweet Corn De Michiel, Helen, 1990; V-6199; Length: 00:50:00 (Box 7)
  - Yanomani Indian Downey, Juan, 1976-1978; V-6200; Length: 00:30:00 (Box 7)
  - J. S. Bach Downey, Juan, 1986; V-6200; Length: 00:26:00 (Box 7)
  - Guadalcanal Requiem Paik, Nam June, 1977; V-6200; Length: 00:49:00 (Box 7)
  - Interview with Tomkins Paik, Nam June, 1976; V-6200; Length: 00:10:00 (Box 7)
  - The Red Tapes parts 1 & 2 Acconci, Vito, 1977; V-6201; conclusion on separate tape; see V-6223 (Box 7)
  - Global Groove Paik, Nam June, 1973; V-6202; Length: 00:28:00 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Amazing Voyages of Flaubert and Roussel, Part 1 Fagin, Steve, V-6203 (Box 7)
  - Weather Diary 3 Kuchar, George, 1998; V-6203; Length: 00:24:00 (Box 7)
  - I Remember Beverly Hills Segalove, Ilene, 1980; V-6203; Length: 00:28:00 (Box 7)
  - The Lost Notebooks of Amelia Earhart Sweeney, Kathleen and Jeffrey Marino, 1990; V-6204; Length: 00:19:00 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Medium is the Medium Paik, Nam June et al. with WGBH, 1969; V-6205; Length: 00:29:00 (Box 7)
  - Womb with a View Millner, Sherry, 1986; V-6206; Length: 00:40:00 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Scenes from the Micro-War Millner, Sherry, 1985; V-6206; Length: 00:24:00 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Listening: A Video Novel in Three Parts Starr, Margot, 1990; V-6206; Length: 00:29:00 (Box 7)
  - Vital Statistics of a Citizen Simply Observed Rosler, Martha, 1977; V-6207; Length: 00:40:00 (Box 7)
  - Girl Power Benning, Sadie, 1992; V-6208; Length: 00:15:00 (Box 7)
  - Jollies Benning, Sadie, 1990; V-6208; Length: 00:06:00 (Box 7)
  - If Every Girl Had a Diary Benning, Sadie, 1990; V-6208; Length: 00:06:00 (Box 7)
  - Welcome to Normal Benning, Sadie, 1990; V-6208; Length: 00:19:00 (Box 7)
  - Me Rubyfruit Benning, Sadie, 1989; V-6208; Length: 00:04:00 (Box 7)
  - Living Inside Benning, Sadie, 1989; V-6208; Length: 00:04:00 (Box 7)
  - A New Year Faber, Mindy, 1993; V-6208; Length: 00:23:00 (Box 7)
  - Delirium Delirium, 1992; V-6208; Length: 00:15:00 (Box 7)
  - Alive from Off Center, 1991; V-6209 (Box 7)
  - Damnation of Faust Birnbaum, Dara, V-6209 (Box 7)
  - Interview Viola, Bill, 1982; V-6210; Length: 00:14:00 (Box 7)
  - Interview Birnbaum, Dara, 1982; V-6210; Length: 00:15:00 (Box 7)
  - Interview Hill, Gary, 1981; V-6210; Length: 00:08:00 (Box 7)
  - The Bus Stops Here Zando, Julie and Jo Anstey, 1990; V-6211; Length: 00:27:00 (Box 7)
  - Allan ‘n’ Allen’s Complaint Paik, Nam June, 1982; V-6212; Length: 00:29:00 (Box 7)
  - Emergence Parmar, Pratibha, 1986; V-6212; Length: 00:19:00 (Box 7)
  - Belladonna Appleborg, Ida and Beth B., 1989; V-6213; Length: 00:12:00 (Box 7)
  - Measures of Distance Hatoum, Mona, 1988; V-6213; Length: 00:15:00 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Greg Ulmer Reads Reading on TV Ulmer, Greg and Paper Tiger TV, 1992; V-6214; Length: 00:28:00 (Box 7)
  - Video SEWA: A People’s Alternative, V-6214; Length: 00:15:00 (Box 7)
  - Cauliflower Alley Tapes parts 1 & 2 Darling, Lowell and Ilene Segalove, 1976; V-6215; Length: 00:70:00 (Box 7)
  - Knowing Her Place Krishnan, Indu, 1990; V-6216; Length: 00:40:00 (Box 7)
  - I Don’t Know What It is I Am Like Viola, Bill, 1986; V-6217; Length: 00:90:00 (Box 8)
  - Let’s Play Prisoners Zando, Julie, 1988; V-6218; Length: 00:20:00 (Box 8)
  - Amazing Voyages of Flaubert and Roussel, Part 2 Fagin, Steve, V-6218 (Box 8)
  - Memories from the Department of Amnesia Tanaka, Janice, 1989; V-6219; Length: 00:13:00 (Box 8)
  - Why I Got into TV and Other Stories Segalove, Ilene, 1983; V-6220; Length: 00:11:00 (Box 8)
  - Hitchcock Trilogy Tajiri, Rea, 1987; V-6221; Length: 00:19:00 (Box 8)
  - Off Limits Tajiri, Rea, 1988; V-6221; Length: 00:07:30 (Box 8)
  - Off Limits and Hitchcock Trilogy Tajiri, Rea, 1987-1988; V-6222 (Box 8)
  - Peggy and Fred in Kansas Thornton, Leslie, 1987; V-6222; Length: 00:11:00 (Box 8)
  - Birth of a Candy Bar Miller, Branda, 1988; V-6222; Length: 00:29:00 (Box 8)
  - Time and Space Concepts I, p. II Paik, Nam June and Merce Cunningham, V-6223; Length: 00:27:00 (Box 8)
  - A Spy in the House that Ruth Built Green, Vanalyne, 1989; V-6224; Length: 00:30:00 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - New Year Soe, Valerie, 1987; V-6225; Length: 00:20:00 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Trick or Drink Green, Vanalyne, 1985; V-6225; Length: 00:20:00 (2 copies) (Box 8)
  - Damaged Visions Gorewitz, Shalom, 1991; V-6226; Length: 00:08:00 (Box 8)
  - November Nine Petzall, Jill, 1990; V-6226; Length: 00:07:45 (Box 8)
  - History and Memory Tajiri, Rea, 1991; V-6226; Length: 00:32:00 (Box 8)
  - Who’s Gonna Pay for these Doughnuts Anyway? Tanaka, Janice, 1992; V-6227; Length: 00:58:00 (Box 8)
  - Alive From Off Center: Voguing, Days of Waiting, Color Schemes, V-6228 (Box 8)
  - Mouth to Mouth Theresa Hak Kyung Cha, 1976; V-6229; Length: 00:08:00 (Box 3)
  - Videoeme Theresa Hak Kyung Cha, 1976; V-6229; Length: 00:03:00 (Box 8)
  - Redisappearing Theresa Hak Kyung Cha, V-6229 (Box 8)
  - Untitled Theresa Hak Kyung Cha, V-6229 (Box 8)
  - Reveile la Blume Theresa Hak Kyung Cha, V-6229 (Box 8)
  - Secret Spill Theresa Hak Kyung Cha, V-6229 (Box 8)
  - Ripples Theresa Hak Kyung Cha, V-6229 (Box 8)
  - Alive from Off Center press preview: “Words on Fire,” “The Myth of Modern Dance,” “La Chambre,” “Mass,” “Tango Tango”, 1990; V-6230 (Box 8)
  - Digressions on Unity Gorewitz, Shalom, V-6231 (Box 8)
  - A Small Jubilee Gorewitz, Shalom, 1987; V-6231; Length: 00:08:00 (Box 8)
  - After the Storm Gorewitz, Shalom, 1988; V-6231; Length: 00:10:00 (Box 8)
  - Jerusalem Road Gorewitz, Shalom, 1989; V-6231; Length: 00:03:00 (Box 8)
  - The End of Television Gorewitz, Shalom, 1988; V-6231 (Box 8)
  - Super 8 Compilation Ahwesh, Peggy, V-6232 (Box 8)
  - From Romance to Ritual Ahwesh, Peggy, V-6232 (Box 8)
  - I Ride a Pony Named Flame Ahwesh, Peggy, V-6232 (Box 8)
  - Martinas Playhouse Ahwesh, Peggy, V-6232 (Box 8)
  - There Was an Unseen Cloud Moving Thornton, Leslie et al., 1988; V-6233; Length: 00:60:00 (Box 8)
  - Global Groove Paik, Nam June, V-6234; multiple copies (Box 8)
  - ACM SIGGRAPH ’89 Exhibition of Computer Art: Catalog of Interactive Installations and Video, 1988; V-6235 (Box 8)
  - The Lost Notebooks of Amelia Earhart Sweeney, Kathleen and and Jeffrey Marino, 1990; V-6236; multiple copies (Box 8)
  - Peggy and Fred in Hell Thornton, Leslie, V-6237 (Box 8)
  - Peggy and Fred in Kansas Thornton, Leslie, 1987; V-6237; Length: 00:11:00 (Box 8)
  - Second Peggy and Fred in Hell: 1984-1990 Thornton, Leslie, V-6237; Length: 00:84:00 (Box 8)
  - Out of the Mouth of Babes Millner, Sherry and Ernest Larsen, 1988; V-6238; Length: 00:25:00 (Box 8)
    fragile tape
  - Measures of Distance Hatoum, Mona, 1988; V-6239; Length: 00:15:26 (Box 8)
  - The Mom Tapes 1974-1978, V-6240; Length: 00:28:00 (Box 8)
  - My Puberty Seaglove, Ilene, 1987; V-6241; Length: 00:11:00 (Box 8)
  - Women’s Movements Barbier, Annette, 1989; V-6242; Length: 00:27:30 (Box 8)
  - A New Year Benning, Sadie, 1989; V-6243; Length: 00:04:00 (Box 8)
  - Jollies Benning, Sadie, 1990; V-6243; Length: 00:11:00 (Box 8)
  - If Every Girl had a Diary Benning, Sadie, 1990; V-6243; Length: 00:06:00 (Box 8)
  - Living Inside Benning, Sadie, 1989; V-6243; Length: 00:04:00 (Box 8)
  - Welcome to Normal Benning, Sadie, 1990; V-6243; Length: 00:19:00 (Box 8)
  - Me & Rubyfruit Benning, Sadie, 1989; V-6243; Length: 00:04:00 (Box 8)
  - Beneath the Skin Condit, Cecelia, 1981; V-6244; Length: 00:11:00 (Box 8)
  - Possibly in Michigan Condit, Cecelia, 1983; V-6244; Length: 00:11:40 (Box 8)
  - Not a Jealous Bone Condit, Cecelia, 1987; V-6244; Length: 00:11:00 (Box 8)
  - A Spy in the House that Ruth Built Green, Vanalyne, 1989; V-6245; Length: 00:30:00 (Box 8)
  - Scenes from the Micro-War Millner, Sherry, 1985; V-6246; Length: 00:24:00 (Box 8)
  - Womb with a View Millner, Sherry and Ernsest Larsen, 1986; V-6247; Length: 00:40:00 (Box 8)
  - Jollies, etc. If every Girl Had a Diary Benning, Sadie, V-6248; Length: 00:12:00 (Box 8)